gopconvention2012.com 2012-10-16

# Privacy Policy - 2012 Republican National Convention

This website is operated by the Committee on Arrangements for the 2012 Republican National Convention (“COA”). The COA is committed to protecting the privacy and security of visitors to our website. Outlined below is our online Privacy Policy for information collected through our website and e-mail lists. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at info@gopconvention2012.com.

Because we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Child Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). In accordance with COPPA, the COA does not ask for any personal information from children under the age of 13, nor does it knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

As used herein, the term “personal information” means information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name, address, telephone number, mobile number or e-mail address) and information about that individual or his or her activities that is directly linked to personally identifiable information. Personal information does not include aggregate information, which is data we collect about the use of our website or about a group or category of services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. This Privacy Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information.

Personal information may be collected in a number of ways when you visit our website. For example, we may collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us when you participate in an activity on our website.

In addition, information may also be collected automatically, such as your Internet Protocol address, your operating system or the browser type. We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with, or link it to, any of the identifying information mentioned above; otherwise, it is used only in the aggregate to assess the aggregate level of traffic on our site, including what pages people are visiting, insight on the general geographic area that visitors are coming from (but not information on a specific individual), and to diagnose any potential problems with the website.

We may also collect certain information through the use of cookies or web beacons to help us improve our website and your experience. These files do not access or use information by which users can be personally identified. If you wish, you can prevent these files from using non-personal information about you by either deleting the cookie folder in your browser or by putting your browser’s Privacy setting higher, but doing so may well adversely affect your experience of our website and others that use cookies to enhance or personalize that experience.

Under no circumstances will the COA sell your information to commercial entities or other third parties. The COA, however, may share information provided by you with authorized third parties required to deliver a particular service. These third parties may not use said information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for the COA.

Our site may contain links to other websites and servers. The COA does not bear responsibility for privacy policies or content on linked websites. Accordingly, you also agree and acknowledge that the COA will not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance of any such content, services on or through any such website or resource or goods. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on each website you visit.

Should you wish to opt-out of receiving text messages or email updates from the COA, an “Unsubscribe” link is included in every such communication. If your link is not working properly, or you wish to communicate your desire to opt-out directly to us, please email info@gopconvention2012.com and include “Unsubscribe” in the subject line.

While we do not intend to make any changes to this Privacy Policy, we do reserve the right to do so. If any changes to this Privacy Policy are made, then the date that the revised or updated policy is posted to our website will appear at the bottom of the page.

_Updated: October 17, 2011_
